RESUME

MAHESH B PRAJAPATI

125-AB Anandpark Society, Grid Road, Kabilpore, Navsari-396445, Gujarat, India

(C) +91 8469695169 mahesh311094@gmail.com

CAREER OBJECTIVES

I have 4 years of experience in this field, I will know about the nature of my work. Moreover, I will attempt to know about the various processes which form my job. By doing so, I will be able to do my job more proficiently. On the other hand, shall implement my knowledge into the practical world.

EDUCATIONAL QUALIFICATION

Name of Examination	Board/ University	Percentage	Passing Year
B.E. (C.S.E)	G.T.U	C.G.P.A: 6.77	May 2016
H.S.C	GSHSEB	55.00 %	March 2012
S.S.C	GSHSEB	71.38 %	March 2010

TECHNICAL SKILL

PROGRAMMING LANG.	ANDROID, JAVA, KOTLIN, FLUTTER, DART	
Web Technology	PHP, CodeIgniter, HTML, JS	
Database	SQLite, MYSQL, MSSQL	

WORK EXPERIENCE

- Currently working (Remote Work) in Shalooka plc, London, UK as a Team lead software developer from May 2018 to present
- ❖ I have 1 year of experience as senior android developer in **Ddeveloper, Surat** from June 2017- May 2018.
- ❖ I have 1 year of experience as android developer in Tech-fusion technologies, Navsari from June 2016 - May 2017.

PORTFOLIO

Android App: -

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.shalooka.marketplace&hl=en

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.plentika.community&hl=en

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=jo.basket&hl=en

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.androidapp.watchme&hl=en

Website: -

https://www.shalooka.com

https://stallionsmultiservices.com

Extra curriculum activities

2019 – team Runners-up in Smart India Hackathon held by Indian Government.

2018 – Runners-up in **Code gladiators Mobility Hackathon** held by **Techgig** and selected as a software developer in **Reliance JIO** company.

PERSONAL PROFILE

Date of Birth	31 st October, 1994
Permanent Address	125-ab Anandpark Society, Grid Road, Kabilpore, Navsari-396445, Gujarat, India
Mobile No.	+91 8469695169
E-mail	mahesh311094@gmail.com
Gender	Male
Marital status	Married
Languages known	English, Hindi, Gujarati
Nationality	Indian

DECLARATION

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is true to the best of my knowledge. I will try to work as well as you expect on me.

THANK YOU

-MAHESH B PRAJAPATI